// Sample quiz data
// TODO: Remove this file once Quiz service is ready
export const testQuiz = [
  {
    title: "Diwali Special",
    createdAt: "11-11-1010",
    updatedAt: "11-11-1010",
    status: 1,
    publishedBy: "test user",
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the capital of India?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt1",
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question:
          "The tropic of cancer does not pass through which of these Indian states ?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt2",
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt3",
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt1",
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt2",
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt4",
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt3",
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt1",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Christmas Special",
    createdAt: "11-11-1010",
    updatedAt: "11-11-1010",
    status: 0,
    publishedBy: "test user",
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the capital of India?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt1",
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question:
          "The tropic of cancer does not pass through which of these Indian states ?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt2",
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt3",
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt1",
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt2",
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt4",
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt3",
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "test2 question?",
        option1: "opt1",
        option2: "opt2",
        option3: "opt3",
        option4: "opt4",
        ans: "opt1",
      },
    ],
  },
];
